NAME
    gcloud beta services mcp - list, enable and disable MCP endpoints

SYNOPSIS
    gcloud beta services mcp GROUP | COMMAND [GCLOUD_WIDE_FLAG ...]

DESCRIPTION
    (BETA) List, enable and disable MCP endpoints.

GCLOUD WIDE FLAGS
    These flags are available to all commands: --help.

    Run $ gcloud help for details.

GROUPS
    GROUP is one of the following:

     content-security
        (BETA) Get/add/remove MCP content security.

COMMANDS
    COMMAND is one of the following:

     disable
        (BETA) Disable a service for MCP on a project, folder or organization.

     enable
        (BETA) Enable a service for MCP on a project, folder or organization.

     list
        (BETA) List MCP services for a project, folder or organization.

NOTES
    This command is currently in beta and might change without notice.

